fashionizers.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy « fashionizers.com

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail  
address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support  
needs)  
**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when  
you enter, submit, or access your personal information.  
**Do we use cookies?**  
We do not use cookies.  
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This  
does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or  
servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release  
your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies,  
or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information  
may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.  
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no  
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to  
protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the  
California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to  
outside parties without your consent.  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do  
not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all  
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  
**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information  
collected offline.  
**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of  
liability governing the use of our website at  
**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.  
**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the  
Privacy Policy modification date below.  
This policy was last modified on 2/28/12  
**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
http://www.fashionizers.com  
9425 E Hidden Spur Trail  
Scottsdale, AZ 85255-6071  
USA
